德古拉  前情提要
Previously on "Dracula"...
- 你认为是谁送的？  - 你送的花啊
- Who do you think might have sent them? - They're from you.
是
Yes.
我促其进程
I refined the process.
你最终会行于日下
You will finally be able to walk in sunlight.
杀害  酷刑  强奸  众多屠戮
Murder, torture, rape, wholesale slaughter...
这就是恶龙会所做的勾当
That is the stock and trade of the Order of the Dragon.
从目前我们展示的
From the moment we demonstrate
磁技术的可能性来看
the viability of geomagnetic technology...
恶龙会将不复存在
No more Order of the Dragon.
好消息  卫生局已经解除了隔离
Great news. The Board of Health, they've removed the quarantine.
欢迎你  Harker先生
Welcome, Mr. Harker.
我以今生起誓  我将始终以
I swear on my life I won't ever place my own needs
神圣的龙之会利益为上  上帝佑吾
above those of this sacred Order, so help me God.
从今夜起  直至
From this night and every
他们屈服  这里将会血流成河
night until they yield, blood will flow.
Grayson
Grayson.
好好享受吧  孩子们
Bon appmotite, boys.
这是Kaha Ruma  我们的猎人首领
This is Kaha Ruma, our leading huntsman.
- 我已经召唤了西西里人  - Loiza Scaverra？
- I've summoned the Sicilian. - Loiza Scaverra?
你需要好的先知
You'll need a good seer.
孩子！
The children!
谁会带走我的孩子们？
Who in God's name would take my children?
你该不会不知道Browning的两个孩子
You wouldn't happen to know anything about the disappearance
- 消失的事儿吧  - 这关你什么事？
- ...of Browning's two children? - What is it to you?
是Grayson  对吧？
It was Grayson, wasn't it?
是他唆使你来找我的？
Goaded you into confronting me?
- 你爱我吗？  - 别这样问我
- Do you love me? - Don't ask me that.
Jonathan
Jonathan.
- Jonathan  为什么？ - 因为你爱Grayson
- Jonathan, why? - Because you love Grayson.
如果你想行如野兽
If you insist on behaving like a monster,
那么我成全你
then I'm going to make you one.
女士们先生们
You do not wanna miss this,
你们不会想错过这个的
ladies and gentlemen.
未来已至
The future has arrived.
今夜  伦敦市民将拥有历史性的机遇
Tonight, the citizens of London will have a historic opportunity
现在即未来
亲眼目睹  无线能源
to see for themselves the wonder of clean, wireless electricity.
来吧  都来吧  加入我们
Come one, come all, join me.
Alexander Grayson会…
Alexander Grayson...
兹邀请您光临Alexander Grayson先生
非同寻常的地磁力展示
先生 Van Helsing教授来这儿为您输液
Sir, Dr. Van Helsing is here to administer your infusion.
把他带到地窖  我等会儿去找他
Show him to the cellar. I'll join him there.
我非常期待看到
I am very much looking
明天的财经版报纸
forward to seeing the financial pages tomorrow.
我想石油价格会下滑啊
I suspect a precipitous drop in the price of oil.
是的  我期待如此
Yes. I expect so.
因为我的直接行动
He's just being testy
他有点儿性急了
because I was right about direct engagement.
没这必要  你已经坚持实施计划了
It wouldn't have been necessary, had you adhered to the plan.
计划…计划
The plan... the plan.
该死的计划实施太长久了
The accursed plan was taking too long.
如果不是因为我
Were it not for me,
共振器就不会被解禁
the resonator would not have
我们的计划也不会回入正轨
been released and our plan now back on track.
所以Abraham
So, Abraham,
为何不和我们一起共谋大事
why don't you motor to the big event with us?
晚会儿吧  等我把这儿处理好
Later, as soon as I finish here.
鄙人事务缠身
I have much to do.
啊…
Ah...
还有个小事儿
What about that other little problem...
Browning家的孩子怎么样了？
Mr. Browning's children?
我想你已经解决了
I take it you've resolved that?
警方又联系你了？
Have the police again contacted you?
你在报纸上看到什么了？
Have you seen anything in the newspapers?
啥也没有  先生
Not a word, sir.
很好
Very well.
稍后你会过来  是吧
You'll be along, then?
你不会想错过
You wouldn't want to miss the
我们强大的敌人跪倒的时刻
moment we bring our greatest enemy to his knees.
我会享受每时每刻的
I will savor every second of it.
我保证
I assure you.
别！关了百叶窗
No! Close the shutters.
我头疼得厉害
I have a shattering headache.
也许我得打电话给Hubert医生
Perhaps I should call Dr. Hubert?
不！不要找医生
No! No doctors.
我就想多睡会儿
I just need some sleep.
拜托了  妈妈  答应我…别找医生
Please, mama, promise me... No doctors.
好  但如果你明天没有好展
Very will, but I will,
我还会叫医生
if you haven't improved by tomorrow.
好  明天
Yes. Tomorrow.
你来干什么
What are you doing here?
我以为
I thought... um...
我以为你出去了
- I didn't think you'd be in.
我…我正准备出去
I was... I was just on my way out.
我想把这个给你
Um, I wanted to give you this.
不用
No.
- 这是你母亲的 - 我不想要
- It was your mother's. - I don't want it.
我无法将它送给别人
I could never bear to see it on anyone else.
我本以为这里某天会成为我们的家
I thought someday this would be our home.
我警告过你要远离他
I warned you to stay away from him.
你不明白
You don't understand...
不  不明白的是你  你看不出来吗
No, you don't understand. Can't you see?
Grayson毁了我
Grayson's ruined me.
迫使我干些卑鄙的事
Made me do things, vile things,
而他也将这样对你
and he'll do exactly the same to you.
- 不是那样的  - 那就向我发誓
- It's not like that. - Then swear to me.
以你母亲的名义向我发誓
Swear to me on your mother's grave
你不爱他
that you don't love him.
所以你明天会去集会
I take it you'll be at the grand demonstration?
很好
Good.
Grayson先生！
Mr. Grayson!
- Grayson先生 - Grayson先生
- Mr. Grayson! - Mr. Grayson!
欢迎 欢迎大家
Welcome one, welcome all!
- Grayson先生 - 很高兴见到您  先生
- Mr. Grayson. - Lovely to meet you, sir.
最终检查  正在进行
Running final checks. We're on schedule.
- 灯光设置如何 - 同计划的一样
- Light rigs? - Going up as we speak.
午夜  这里一半的地方会亮如白昼
00 P.M., and half the district will be lit up as bright as day.
太棒了  Kowalski先生  太棒了
Splendid, Mr. Kowalski. Splendid.
Renfield先生  有Harker先生的消息吗
Mr. Renfield, any word from Mr.
他消失两天了
Harker? He's been missing for two days.
找不到他
We've been unable to locate him.
有消息了  直接带他来见我
When you do locate him, bring him directly to me.
是  先生
I will, sir.
猎人们  请注意
Huntsmen, your attention please.
我相信你们都听过传说中的先知者
I'm sure you've all heard of our legendary seer?
Loiza Scaverra
Loiza Scaverra.
这就是
There it is.
奉主之名
Il sangue di Cristo.
基督之血
The blood of Christ.
基督界最神圣的遗物
The most sacred relic in Christendom.
我们的策略是这样的
Our tactics are as follows.
先知者会利用圣物来找到吸血鬼巢穴
Our seer will utilize this relic to locate the nests.
你们2到3人一组行动
You will be dispatched in teams of two or three.
然后发送信号给我们
You will then signal to us.
每杀死一个发一个信号
One flare per kill.
- 明白了吗 - 是
- Do you understand? - Yes.
那以我们救世主的信念和血起誓
Then by the will and the blood of our savior,
今天我们将消灭吸血鬼和他的子孙
today we will annihilate the Fell One and his spawn.
是
Yes!
翻译：依依  幸福ing形式
翻译：小鱼  资本论and圣经
翻译：Sin-city  老马
监制：幸福ing形式
真爱字幕组
恭祝湘姐新婚快乐
德古拉  第一季第十集
——— 季终集 ———
真 爱 字 幕 组
—— 出  品 ——
你去哪儿了
Where have you been?
我找了你两天
I've been tryin' to contact you for two days.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
你一定知道Davenport大人的事吧
You must have heard about lord Davenport.
那个混蛋…
What does that bastard have to do with...
不
Oh, no.
Harker 你
Harker, you didn't!
我不知道发生了什么事
I don't know what came over me.
我喝高了
I've been drinking.
整件事 都记不清了
The whole thing, it's a blur.
只知道我做了可怕的事
Except I've done some dreadful things.
- 很可怕的事 - Harker
- Some terrible things. - Harker!
镇定
Pull yourself together.
有人看见了吗
Did anyone see you?
- 没有 - 很好
- No one saw. - Good.
听我说
Now, you listen to me.
如果不想被抓
If you don't want to get caught,
就什么都不要管
you're gonna put everything else aside
交给我
and trust me completely.
明白吗
Can you do that?
首先  你要如往常一样生活
First, you're gonna have to deal with things as you always have.
- 我做不到  - 你必须这样做！
- I don't think I can. - You must!
报社的人就在外面
There are press outside,
你必须把他们应付过去
and you have to deal with them
就像你往常所做的那样
as you've always dealt with them.
你能做到吗
Can you do that?
能
Yes.
听着  我理解你的感受
Look, I know how you feel,
但如果能把这几天应付过去
but if you can get through this day,
你就没事了
you're gonna be fine.
现在…摆平这一切  去吧
Now... get cleaned up. Get to work.
你能看到多少吸血鬼？
How many vampires can you see?
确切数字依然影影绰绰
Total is still in shadow.
仿佛暗夜中的群星  实在太多…
All the stars in the heavens. There are so many...
那好  替我找出一个
Well, find me one
并告诉我它在何处
and tell me where it is.
灼灼圣迹  凭彼之血
Holy relic, through your blood
恶灵所隐  示于臣仆
show me where the vampires are hiding.
她叫Ruma  在Lower街95号
Ruma, 95 Lower Street.
猎人们  出发！
Huntsmen, come on!
快！
Hurry!
两道猎迹  把这个告诉Jayne女士
Two flairs. Take this down to Lady Jayne.
遵命  先生
Yes, sir.
先生  给您的口信
Message for you, sir.
- 具体是什么？- 一无所获
- What is it? - Nothing of any consequence.
你要走了？
You're leaving?
你看来是在这惹了麻烦
You seem to have matters in hand here.
两道绿色猎迹！Lower街95号！
Two green flairs! 95 Lower Street.
双杀！
Two kills!
先生 出了什么事？
Sir, is something wrong?
死亡即将造访
Death is coming.
Alexander 这些 额
Alexander, these, um...
- 这些人 他们想要… - 要什么？
- These men, they wish... - What?
你们到底想要什么？
What do you want?
他们…他们是泰晤士报的
They're... They're from The Times.
他们想为特殊的明天拍一下…
They wish to photograph the resonator for...
共振器的照片
A special feature.
Grayson先生 您若不介意?
Mr. Grayson, if you don't mind?
明白
I see.
伦敦泰晤士报的贵客
The Times of London.
欢迎各位到来  请随意
Welcome, gentlemen. Fire away.
你小子犯什么病?
What's wrong with you?
我已经竭尽所能了…
Look, I'm trying the best I...
淡定点
Pull yourself together, man.
我告诉过你  保持镇定
I told you, stay calm.
一切都会水到渠成
It'll all be fine.
几点了?
Time?
四点半
Half past 4:00.
Van Helsing在哪？
Where's Van Helsing?
你去
Go.
跟着他  我受够了
Track him down. I don't like this.
她有点精神崩溃了
She's had some kind of nervous collapse.
她已准备打包走人
She got a package.
Agnetta?
Agnetta  发生了什么？
Agnetta, what has happened?
他说他将每天送一块儿
He says he'll send another piece every day.
什么？ 一块什么？
A what? Another what?
你…
You...
你这个杂种！
You bastard!
他们都会因你丧命而去的！
They're gone because of you!
你把他们给我找回来！
You have to find them!
教授！
Professor!
这里发生了什么？
What is going on here?
我…
I...
我不知道
I have no idea.
我不过是出去了一趟  然后  我
I just stepped outside, and then I, uh...
我就听到这巨响了
I hear this terrible crashing.
对于Grayson来说我已经没用了
I have no more use for Grayson,
现在  日光疫苗已经被毁
and now the solar vaccine has been destroyed,
Grayson将永远无法行走于日光之下
and Grayson will never walk in sunlight again...
你也是
Much like yourself.
- Grayson先生！- Grayson先生！
- Grayson, sir! - Mr. Grayson!
Grayson先生  Grayson先生对那些声称
Mr. Grayson, Mr. Grayson, what do you say
您的新发明不安全的人
to those who claim your contraption
您要说点什么
isn't safe?
他们不过是惧怕改变
They're afraid of change.
如果您对自己的发明的看法是对的
If you are right about your technology,
您认为爱迪生对此将如何反应？
how do you think Mr. Edison will react?
好的  介于他并未向鄙厂投资
Well, considering he chose not to invest in my company,
实在遗憾  我打赌
gravely disappointed, I'd wager.
一年之内我们将把那混蛋赶出这个行业
We'll put the scoundrel out of business by year's end.
真的如此？
Is that a fact?
也许你现在应去准备准备
Perhaps you should go prepare the demonstration.
Grayson先生！ 请看这里
Mr. Grayson! Over here, please.
Grayson先生  他们说你的技术
Mr. Grayson, they say your technology
会使上千的石油工人失去工作
will put thousands of men in the petroleum industry out of work.
对此你有什么想对他们说的？
What do you have to say to them?
我会雇佣他们的
I'm hiring.
那个谁！  他在这是干什么的？
You there! What's he doing down there?
先生们  这位是Kowalski先生
Uh, gentlemen, this is Mr. Kowalski.
Grayson的能源计划总工程师
Uh, Grayson energy's chief engineer.
整个工程的大脑
The brains behind the operation.
我不会让他那么做的
I wouldn't put it like that.
他在干嘛
What's he doing?
我只是在重启我的照相机
I was just reloading my camera.
我觉得照片够多了
I think that's enough pictures for now.
我看老板回来你怎么办
See what you can do about getting the boss back in here.
如果要做个计划的话
I'm gonna need his help
我们得需要他的帮助
if we're gonna make the schedule.
当然
Of course.
先生们  这边请
Uh, gentlemen, please.
装好了吗？
Is it set?
装好了  嗯  反极性
It's set, all right. Inverse polarity.
五分钟后等他们开启的时候…嘣
Five minutes after they power up... boom.
“嘣”是什么意思？
What do you mean "Boom"?
我的意思是我不想在这条街
I mean I wouldn't want to be within a street
爆炸的时候还呆在这
of this place when it goes up.
不是只是安排一个故障吗
It was just supposed to malfunction.
这就是计划  孩子
This is the Order, boy.
我们不能手软
We don't take half measures.
Grayson是我们的敌人
Grayson is the enemy.
记住了
Remember that.
Mina
Mina.
Mina！  Mina！
Mina! Mina!
求你一定要在那
Please be here.
Mina…
Mina...
托儿所  我希望我从没做过那种事
nursey, I would never do such a thing.
- 谢谢你  - 你真是个淘气的孩子！
- Thank you. - You're a naughty, naughty boy!
我收到了你的消息
I got your message.
按照你的要求做
I did as you asked.
Rose？
Rose?
Willy？
Willy?
爸爸！
Daddy!
帮帮我们吧！
Help us!
举起手来
Up.
这是什么？
What's this?
我的孩子呢？
Where are my children?
不要慌  你们会很快团聚的
Do not worry. You will be reunited soon enough.
过去
Move.
快走！
Move!
在这就行  这距离够了
Right there. That's far enough.
一动也别动Browning先生
Keep perfectly still, Mr. Browning,
不然我就打死你
or I will shoot you.
我带来了钱  都在这
I brought your money. It's all there.
嗯  我知道
Yes, I'm sure it is.
你不认识我了吗？
Do you not recognize me?
我应该认识你吗？
Should I?
Abraham van Helsing
Abraham van Helsing.
你杀了我全家人
You slaughtered my family.
这很难缩小范围  是么？
That hardly narrows it down, does it?
你是个怪物
You are a monster.
比之前我
More vile than the one I
释放你和你兄弟还卑鄙
have unleashed upon you and your brethren.
Dracula
Dracula.
是的
Yes.
爸爸？
Daddy?
哦  天啊！
Oh, God!
你个混账东西  你会遭报应的！
You bastard. You will pay for this!
等着…
Wait...
什…你个疯子！
Wha... you madman!
我的孩子呢？
Where are my children?
他们很好Browning先生
They're all right, Mr. Browning.
他们在底下等着你呢
They're down there with you.
只是有点害羞
They're just a little shy.
Rose？
Rose?
Rose  出来  宝贝
Rose, come out, sweetheart.
是我  爸爸
It's me, it's daddy.
哦  感谢上帝
Oh, thank God.
哦  宝贝Rose
Oh, dear Rose.
你哥哥呢？
Where's your brother?
这呢  爸爸
Here, daddy.
哦  William  对不起
Oh, William, I'm so sorry.
很痒
It itches.
来  来我这
Come. Come to me.
来爸爸这里
Come to your father.
不
No...
不要啊
No. No!
我用Dracula的血喂了你的孩子
I fed your children Dracula's blood.
现在他们可以尽情享用你拉
Now they can feed on you.
多谢了  先生
Oh, thank you, sir.
Mina
Mina!
我是Alexander Grayson
I'm Alexander Grayson.
我确信到现在为止
I'm sure by now some of you
你们已经注意到台阶上的电子设备了
have noticed the electrical devices on the stage
除此之外  我们在外面也安装了这些设备
as well as those we have
整个区域到处都是
installed outside and throughout the district.
你们从不问问自己
Some of you no doubt have asked yourselves,
他们是怎么把全部设备
how did they wire all these devices
用一天就全接上线了
in one single day?
答案出奇地简单
The answer is as astonishing as it is simple.
他们根本不需要用到电线
They need no wires...
你们马上看到的突破成果
For the breakthrough you are about to see
就是第一台无线电传播装置
is the first practical transmission of wireless electricity.
Vedo Dracula.
- 我看到他了  - 在哪儿  他在哪儿啊
- I see him. - Where? Where is he?
他就在河边
Down by the river...
站在人群前面
Standing before a vast crowd of humans.
Grayson.
夫人
Senora...
这是从教皇军械处得来的另一份礼物
Another gift from the papal armory.
去码头  现在出发  快点儿
To the docks. Now! Go!
八个月前  我来到了伦敦
Eight months ago I arrived in London
招募世界顶尖的科学奇才
to engage the world's leading scientific minds,
这些人可以看到未来
men who had a vision of the future.
人们像我一样  将看到理想化为现实
Men determined, like me, to see that vision become a reality
为全人类造福  Mina
to the benefit of all mankind. Mina!
我的一位挚友
A dear friend of mine
她说最近很欣赏我的坦诚
recently told me that she admired my honesty.
- 给我们看看  - Mina
- Show us! - Mina!
- 给我们瞧瞧  - 给我们瞧瞧
- Show us! - Show us!
瞧瞧  瞧瞧  瞧瞧  瞧瞧
Show us, show us, show us, show us, show us!
Mina  咱们得快离开这
Mina, we have to get out of here.
- 干嘛  - 那个共振器
- What? - The resonator.
五分钟前刚被设置为引爆状态
Five minutes from when it's switched on it's set to explode.
Kowalski先生
Mr. Kowalski.
第一步
Stage one...
启动
Mark.
到底怎么了
What have you done?
给我们看看  给我们看看  给我们看看...
Show us, show us, show us, show us...
没时间说了
There's no time.
-走开  别挡道 - 别推我
- Move! Out of my way! - Don't push me!
第二步  启动！
Stage two... Mark!
停下来  快停止演示
Stop! Stop the demonstration!
有人动过手脚
It's been sabotaged.
这台机器被动过手脚了
The machine has been sabotaged.
你得把它关掉
You have to shut it down.
谁动的手脚
Sabotaged by who?
我也不清楚  Jonathan刚告诉我的
I don't know. Jonathan's just told me.
Harker.
把它关掉
Shut it down!
没反应！
She's not responding!
快点
Come on.
Mina  我们快离开这
Mina, we have to get out of here.
别碰我
Don't touch me!
看看你做了什么
What did you do?
那台发电机
The generator.
我们把线绕过来
We reversed the wires.
快带她离开这
Get her out of here now.
Mina  跟着Harker走！
Mina! Go with Harker!
- 不  - 跟着Harker走
- No. - Go with Harker!
不  不  不  不
No, no, no, no!
马上带所有人离开这
Get everyone out of here right now
要爆炸了
before the place explodes!
快  大家快跑
Come on! Everybody out!
- 快走  走  - Alexander
- Get out of here! Move! - Alexander!
Alexander
Alexander!
啊
Aah!
好了  保持冷静
That's it, stay calm.
Alexander  Alexander
Alexander? Alexander!
- 他已经死了   - 不
- He's dead. - No...
- 他死了  - 不
- He's dead. - No!
- 他不可能活着  - 不  这不可能
- He wouldn't have survived. - No! No!
Mina
Mina.
你是个杀人犯
You're a murderer.
是你杀了他和这些无辜的人
You murdered him and all these innocent people.
Szabo
Szabo...
Szabo.
哦 天哪
Oh, my God.
Grayson
Grayson!
Grayson  你个混蛋
Grayson, you bastard.
我知道你还活着
I know you're still alive.
嗨  Jayne
Hello, Jayne.
- 我知道你是谁  - 你从心底
- I know who you are. - You've always known.
一直都知道
Deep down.
承认吧
Admit it.
走吧 Jayne
Walk away, Jayne.
离开我
From me.
离开他们
From them.
好好活着
Live.
生命是宝贵的
Life is precious.
不
No.
居然用枪
Guns.
这样才像话
That's more like it.
我以为你爱我
I thought you loved me.
我骗你的
I lied.
对不住了  Jayne
Sorry, Jayne.
你这些玩意儿对我都不管用
I've grown immune to all your toys.
我了解你的内心
I know what's inside you.
黑暗
The darkness.
我生活在黑暗中
I live in the darkness...
但是我渴望光明
But I yearn for the light,
即使受伤
even though it burns.
我想要那样的生活
I want life.
你认为你能躲过Mina Murray这个劫吗
And you think that you can live through Mina Murray?
你从来都不是她想要的人
You can never be what she needs...
你个不死的怪物
You undead thing.
杀了我吧
Kill me.
求求你
Please.
别把我变成吸血鬼
Don't turn me.
你欠我的
You owe me that.
妈妈
Mother?
妈
Mama...?
妈妈  来这儿  亲亲我
Come to me, mother. Kiss me.
Lucy  我很担心你
Lucy, I was so worried.
抱着我  妈妈 抱着我
Hold me, mama. Hold me now.
哦  我的宝贝
Oh, my darling.
哦  我以为我永远失去你了
Oh, I thought I had lost you forever.
Alexander
Alexander?
Mina
Mina.
Aleander
Alexander.
我好害怕我就这么失去你了
I was so afraid that I had lost you.
我在这儿
I'm here.
我一直都在这儿
I'll always be here.
Ilona
Ilona.
从我记事起
She's someone I've always loved,
她就是我的挚爱
as long as I can remember.
- 从过去就是 - 嗯
- From a past life? - Yes.
从过去就是
From a past life.
直到此时此刻
And here, now.
怎么会这样
But how?
我也不知道
I don't know.
从第一次见到你
I've asked myself that same
我也问过自己这个问题
question since first I laid my eyes on you.
太神奇了
By some miracle.
- 我收到了你的信  - Harker先生
- I got your message. - Mr. Harker.
请坐
Please, have a seat.
关于Grayson你知道些什么
What can you tell me about Grayson?
所有足以让你毁了他的事
Everything you need to know to destroy him.
他的名字
His name...
是Dracula
Is Dracula.